<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_p1">This privacy notice tells you what to expect when we collect personal information. It applies to information we collect about:</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_website">Visitors to our websites</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_website_p1">When someone visits one of our websites, we store web server log information, which includes information such as the IP address you connected from, the user agent of your browser and which page you requested. We use this information to monitor the security, performance and health of our systems. All of our websites are protected by TLS. This means your connection to our websites is encrypted.</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_attendees">People who register and attend our events</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_attendees_p1">If you have registered for our events, we store the personal information about you, which was either provided by you or someone from your organization who gave us permission to provide us this information.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_attendees_p2">This information includes your full name, email address, location, and government ID, which we require to grant you access to the conference. Additional information associated with your ticket may be requested but not required. This includes job title, company name, among others. We ask for the additional optional information because it helps us better understand the profile of our attendees and ensure the high quality of the overall event experience is relevant to our audience. For example, we ask for your job title to confirm that we include content in the program that is relevant to your job role. We may also ask for your dietary restrictions and preferences to ensure we order appropriate food in the right quantities. We may also use your contact information including email address and phone number to contact you with important information related to the event or in case of emergencies.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_attendees_p3">Leading up to the event, you may receive emails that include practical information related to the event including registration hours, links to additional social events and new speaker announcements. After the event, you may receive an email requesting event feedback and including links to watch event videos online. Emails both before and after the event may also contain information about upcoming free community events and other information relevant for attendees.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_attendees_p4">Each of our marketing communications provides you with the options to unsubscribe or alter your communication preferences. You do have the option to unsubscribe from the practical information emails but we strongly encourage you to keep this subscription so we can email you with important practical information for you as an attendee of the event.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_attendees_p5">During the event, your personal information will be temporarily stored on our on-site registration and printed out so that the security personnel can grant you access to the event.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_attendees_p6_pt1">Your picture may be taken during the event and published on our social and marketing channels. Please make yourself known to the organizing team if you do not wish to have your picture taken during the event. If you find an unwanted picture of yourself on any of our channels, please email us at </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_attendees_p6_pt2"> with the link to the photo and we will take it down.</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers">People who are speaking at one of our events</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers_p1">When you are speaking at one of our events, we do need some personal information in order to communicate with you, arrange travel and accommodation, or ensure other practical details related to your appearance at our event.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers_p2">This information includes your full name, email, phone number and country of residence. We may share this information with third parties when it is required for fulfilling our agreement with you. For instance, we may need to share your name and email with a hotel to book a room for you during the event. We also need some information in order to publish and market your talk on our website. This information includes your name, company name, profile picture, speaker bio, social media profile links, links to your blog(s) or website(s) as well as the title and description for the talk(s) and/or workshop(s) you will perform at our event.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers_p3">During the event, attendees have the ability to submit feedback in the form of ratings, comments and questions about your talk through surveys. This feedback will be monitored by our team members during the event, and the questions during your talk will be relayed to you in front of the audience at the end of the talk if there is time.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers_p4">We use this information to gather general feedback about the event, review the quality of the topics and talks, and use as input for planning of future conferences. We do not share this information with any third parties.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers_p5_pt1">If logistics allow, we may also record your talk at the conference and collect your slides to publish on our website. We may also publish the recorded video of your talk on </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers_p5_pt2">our YouTube channel</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers_p5_pt3">. We may also promote the video of your talk through various social media channels.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_speakers_p6">Your picture may be taken during the event and published on our social and marketing channels. Please make yourself known to the organizing team if you do not wish to have your picture taken during the event. If you find an unwanted picture of yourself on our channels, please email us at android@devperu.org with a link to the image and we will take it down.</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_sponsors">People who are partners or sponsors</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_sponsors_p1">When you sign on as a partner or sponsor of our events, we collect information in the form of billing details to issue your invoice as per the terms of the partnership agreement. This information includes name, email, company name, company address, phone number and RUC. In cases where we don't receive payment, we may send you payment reminders or reach out to assist with finalising the partnership deal.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_sponsors_p2">We also collect the names, emails and phone numbers of the contact person/s representing our partners (such as the event manager). This is so we can fulfill our obligations detailed in your partnership agreement and keep you informed about key dates and deliverables.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_sponsors_p3_pt1">If your partnership deal contains event tickets or exhibitor passes, you can refer to the </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_sponsors_p3_pt2"> section for specific information related to registration.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_sponsors_p4_pt1">After the conference, we will reach out to you to ask for additional, optional feedback and/or a testimonial, along with the details of upcoming events. You can let us know anytime if you want to opt out of these communications. For more information, you can refer to the </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_sponsors_p4_pt2"> section of this policy.</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_rights">Your Rights</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_complaints">Complaints or queries</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_complaints_p1">We are committed to using best practices to ensure our responsibility when collecting and using personal information, and we take any complaints related to data privacy very seriously. If you think our collection and use of data is unfair, misleading or inappropriate, we encourage you to contact us using the contact information provided at the top of the page.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_access_your_data">Access to your data</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_access_your_data_p1">You have a right to know which information we store and process about you, where it came from, what we use it for and who we share it with.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_access_your_data_p2">You have a right to have incorrect or incomplete information about you corrected or deleted.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_access_your_data_p3">You can exercise these rights by contacting us, and we will do what we can to satisfy your request in a timely manner. For your protection, we may need to verify your identity before responding to your request, such as verifying that the email address from which you send the request matches your email address that we have on file.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_access_your_data_p4">In some cases we may not be able to delete your information if we have another legitimate reason preventing us from doing so, such as the obligation to keep financial records for a certain period of time. Please contact us with any questions or concerns about this.</string>
</resources>